{
    "subject": "resource/Jupiter_Ascending",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_shot_in_Chicago,_Illinois",
    "human_readable": "Jupiter Ascending is a film shot in Chicago, Illinois.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9812887907028198,
            "question": "Is 'Jupiter Ascending' a film set in Chicago?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195412397384644,
            "question": "Where was the film 'Jupiter Ascending' shot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8413106799125671,
            "question": "In which state was 'Jupiter Ascending' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114912509918213,
            "question": "Can you name a film that was shot in Chicago, Illinois?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.775614321231842,
            "question": "What type of movie is 'Jupiter Ascending'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7622418403625488,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Jupiter Ascending'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7342516779899597,
            "question": "What city served as a filming location for 'Jupiter Ascending'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6910325288772583,
            "question": "What is the setting of the film 'Jupiter Ascending'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5978930592536926,
            "question": "Name some actors who appeared in 'Jupiter Ascending'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3054550886154175,
            "question": "What year was 'Jupiter Ascending' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jupiter Ascending is a film shot in Chicago, Illinois.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3265_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name some actors who appeared in 'Jupiter Ascending'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3265_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the setting of the film 'Jupiter Ascending'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3265_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city served as a filming location for 'Jupiter Ascending'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3265_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3265_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that \"Jupiter Ascending was filmed in London in the United Kingdom, Chicago in the United States of America, and in Spain.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3265/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt) and also mention that \"Filming in Chicago for Jupiter Ascending started on July 20\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3265/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt), which confirms that the film was indeed shot in Chicago, Illinois."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the filming of \"Jupiter Ascending\" in various locations, including Chicago, Illinois. Therefore, the statement that \"Jupiter Ascending is a film shot in Chicago, Illinois\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}